(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T10:12:11.324024",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
曖昧3センチ そりゃぷにってコトかい?
Around 3 centimeters, is that squishy?
ちょっと! らっぴんぐが制服
Wait! My wrapping is a uniform...
だぁぁ不利ってコトないぷぅ。
There's no disadvantage to it, phew.
がんばっちゃ? やっちゃっちゃ
Shall I do my best? Do it, do it
そんときゃーっち&Release ぎょっ
In times like that, it's catch & release, gyo
汗(ふう)×(ふう)の谷間に
In the gap between drops of sweat,
Darlin' darlin' F R E E Z E!!
なんかダルー なんかデルー
I feel kinda sluggish, I feel kinda out of it
あいしてルー あれ一個が違ってるーん
I love you; what's that? One piece is different?
なやみん坊ー 高鉄棒ー
Worry-wart, high bar
おいしん笥ー いーかげんにシナサイ
Gourmet, cut it out
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
About the flushed body of that girl who jumped
所謂ふツーのおにゅのこ
She's just a so-called "normal" girl
驚いたあたしだけ?
Am I the only one who was surprised?
豚骨ハリガネおかわりだだだ
Another helping of pig bone wires
BON-BON おーえん団
Bon-bon, we're cheerleaders
Let's get! チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie
RAN-RAN かんげー会
Ran-ran, a welcome party
Look up! せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation
はい! 存在感..小惑星
Yeah! The feeling of existence... asteroids
ぶつかって溶けましたぽーぜん
They collided and melted, dumbfounded
大いに歌ってシレンジャー
Singing loud, four rangers
もっていけ!
Take it!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
The one who laughs last should be me
セーラーふくだからです→結論
Because I'm wearing a sailor suit, that's my conclusion
月曜日なのに! 機嫌悪いのどうする?
Even though it's Monday! I'm in a bad mood, what should I do?
夏服がよいのです→キャ?
Summer clothes are nice, huh? How cute!
イイv 接近3ピクト
Oh my / approaching 3 picts
曖昧3センチ そりゃぷにってコトかい？ちぇっ！
Around 3 centimeters, and that's squishy? Yeah right!
ラッピングが制服…だあい不利ってこたナイぷ。
My uniform wrapping... has no real disadvantage, pb bth.
がんばっちゃ やっちゃっちゃ
I'll give it my best, I'll do it!
そんときゃーっち＆release ぎょっち
Catch & release in moments like that, gyo!
汗々谷間に darlin' darlin' f r e e z e!!
In the valleys of sweat, darlin' darlin' f r e e z e!!
なんかダルー なんかデルー
Feeling sluggish, feeling like something's coming out,
あいしーテルー あれ一個が違ってるーん
I see, teru... Wait, one of them is wrong—
なやみん坊ー 高鉄棒ー
Worrywart, high bar,
おいしーん笥ー いーかげんにシナサイ
gourmet, cut it out!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
About the flushed body of that flying person—
所謂ふふーんのおにゅーのコ
She's just a so-called brand-new girl!
驚いたあたしだけ？ 豚骨ハリガネー おかわりだだだ
Was I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu extra-firm noodles, another round!
bon-bon おーえん団
Bon-bon, cheerleading squad!
let's get！ チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
ran-ran かんげー会
Ran-ran, welcome party!
look up！ せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation!
はい！ 存在感…小惑星
Yeah! The feeling of presence... Asteroid!
ぶつかって溶けました ぼーぜん
They collided and melted, dumbfounded.
大いに 歌ってシレンジャー
Singing loudly, four rangers!
もって いけ！
Take it!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
The one who laughs last should be me,
セーラーふくだからです←結論
because I'm wearing a sailor suit—conclusion!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's Monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm in a bad mood, what should I do?
夏服がいいのです←キャッ！ワ！イイv
Summer clothes are best—Kya! Wa! Good v!
接近3ピクトするまでって ちゅうちょだやん☆
Hesitating until we're within 3 pixels—no way!
がんばって はりきって my darlin' darlin' p l e a s e!!
Do your best, work hard, my darlin' darlin' p l e a s e!!
もりあがりー もりさがりー
High and low spirits,
恋したりー まだ内緒にしといて倫理ー
falling in love, keeping it a secret, morality!
あまえん坊ー 用心坊ー
Spoiled brat, cautious one,
つうしん笥ー ちょーしこいてギョクサイ
report card, getting cocky and crashing!
踏んでったアイツに小指イタイって
Saying my pinky hurts from the one who stepped on it—
大袈裟ちらーり 黒ニーハイ
exaggerated glimpse of black knee-highs!
絶対じゃん 領域じゃん？ 生足ツルピカ おねだりだだだ
Isn't it absolute? Isn't it territory? Smooth bare legs, begging!
mon-mon もーそー伝
Mon-mon, delusions chronicle!
let's go！ パル神殿
Let's go! The Parthenon!
yai-ya！ そーらん節
Yai-ya! Soran bushi!
what's up？ てんぺめでーしょん
What's up? Temptation!
おい！ 喪失感 ￥￥アルバイト
Hey! Loss of feeling, money part-time job!
さがしたら 見つかってーそーぜん
Searching for it, and finding it naturally—
人生 まるっとケネルネーシ
life is totally kennel-nation!
やってみな！
Give it a try!
新規に狙いちゃうのはあたしの挑戦
Aiming for something new is my challenge,
セーラーふく着替えても＝あたし
even when changing into a sailor suit = me!
週末はどうよ？
What about the weekend?
チラみせなんて ありきたり！
A peek of skin is so cliché!
制服はかんたんよ＝ラクチン
Uniforms are simple = easy!
風速3メートル抱きついてがまんがまん、ぎゅ☆
At 3m/s wind speed, clinging and enduring, gyu!
胸どっきん 腰ざっきん i'm sugar sugar s w e e t!!
Heart throbbing, waist rocking, i'm sugar sugar s w e e t!!
bon-bon mon-mon day
let's get！ uh uh ah！
let's get! uh uh ah!
ran-ran chop chop kick
look up！ fu fu ho！
look up! fu fu ho!
hi！ education！！ love is abc
hi! education!! love is abc!
うんだかだー うんだかだー うんいゅーうんいゅー
Undakada, undakada, unyu unyu!
はれっしてほれっして ひれんらー
Clearing up, falling in love, unrequited love!
もって いけ！
Take it!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
The one who laughs last should be me,
セーラーふくだからです←結論
because I'm wearing a sailor suit—conclusion!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's Monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm in a bad mood, what should I do?
夏服がいいのです←キャッ！ワ！イイv
Summer clothes are best—Kya! Wa! Good v!
やっぱりね
As I thought,
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
the one who laughs last should be me,
セーラーふくだからです←結論
because I'm wearing a sailor suit—conclusion!
曖昧3センチ そりゃぷにってコトかい？わお！
Around 3 centimeters, and that's squishy? Wow!
ラッピングが制服…ようし不利ってこたナイぽ。
My uniform wrapping... alright, no disadvantage, po!
がんばっちゃ？ やっちゃっちゃ
Giving it your best? I'll do it!
あんときゃーっぴ＆ジャージでハッ
Back then, cap & jersey, hah!
汗々で透けたら darlin' darlin' a m u s e!!
Seeing through sweaty moments, darlin' darlin' a m u s e!!
なんかダルー なんかデルー
Feeling sluggish, feeling like something's coming out,
あいしーテルー あれ一個が違ってるーん
I see, teru... wait, one of them is wrong!
なやみん坊ー 高鉄棒ー
Worrywart, high bar,
おいしーん笥ー いーかげんにシナサイ
gourmet, cut it out!
飛んでったアイツの火照るカラダって
About the flushed body of that flying person—
所謂ふふーんのおにゅーのコ
she's just a so-called brand-new girl!
驚いたあたしだけ？ 豚骨ハリガネー おかわりだだだ
Was I the only one surprised? Tonkotsu extra-firm noodles, another round!
bon-bon おーえん団
Bon-bon, cheerleading squad!
let's get！ チェリーパイ
Let's get! Cherry pie!
ran-ran かんげー会
Ran-ran, welcome party!
look up！ せんせーしょん
Look up! Sensation!
はい！ 存在感…小惑星
Yeah! The feeling of presence... Asteroid!
ぶつかって溶けました ぼーぜん
They collided and melted, dumbfounded.
大いに 歌ってシレンジャー
Singing loudly, four rangers!
もって いけ！
Take it!
最後に笑っちゃうのはあたしのはず
The one who laughs last should be me,
セーラーふくだからです←結論
because I'm wearing a sailor suit—conclusion!
月曜日なのに！
Even though it's Monday!
機嫌悪いのどうするよ？
I'm in a bad mood, what should I do?
夏服がいいのです←キャッ！ワ！イイv
Summer clothes are best—Kya! Wa! Good v!
接近3ピクトするまでって ちゅうちょだやん☆
Hesitating until we're within 3 pixels—no way!
がんばって はりきって my darlin' darlin' p l e a s e!!
Do your best, work hard, my darlin' darlin' p l e a s e!!
もりあがりー もりさがりー
High and low spirits,
恋したりー まだ内緒にしといて倫理ー
falling in love, keeping it a secret, morality!
あまえん坊ー 用心坊ー
Spoiled brat, cautious one,
つうしん笥ー ちょーしこいてギョクサイ
report card, getting cocky and crashing!
bon-bon mon-mon day
let's get！ uh uh ah！
let's get! uh uh ah!
Oh, this is what I'm talking about!
That's what we need!
We need another hit show!
We need an anime opening!
No, no, we need... no, we need a show.
We need something with substance.
I just thought that our show was failing
because we didn't have an anime opening.
No, our show is failing because it's really bad.
It's... it's not that bad.
It's really bad!
Have you seen the reviews?
I can't afford rent.
What else do we need? Um...
We need to sell out.
We need to sell out. Ugh.
I'm so tired from all this thinking.
I think we need to explore other genres to see the yami green.
Like what?
Every genre. I think that's the only way.
You're only kind of... What?
I'm a sympathetic sleeper.
Huh? Huh?
Where are we, Gigi?
What is this? What is this? Are we... Are we in my head?
Wait, are we in your head?
Are we in my head?
What? This is just fiction!
This is just fiction!
Does it mean we're going to steal Mabel's ideas?
No, they're our ideas. We're in my head.
I'm going to steal your idea!
You can't steal my ideas.
I could.
Wait, what if...
What if I see every single idea that's in your head and then I take them from you and then I kill you?
If you get too deep into my brain, you'll get to the yawi parts!
Oh, oh. I remember we should start with my brain. It's okay, it's okay.
Wait. What's in your brain? Nothing.
Actually, there's a lot in my brain. For example...
Your brain is full of bad romance novels! We can't put that in our show!
Yeah, we can! Let's put it in our show! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Romance... hmm... Romance... Romance...
Guess we need to break free out of this place.
DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL
[Title: DROPPED OUT OF SCHOOL MUSICAL]
THE FOLLOWING SCENE IS AS FOLLOWS: CROY AND GIBRIELLA ARE AT A PARTY. CROY LOVES BASKETBALL AND GIBRIELLA IS NOT LIKE OTHER GIRLS... A FICTIONAL TALE OF SONG AND BASKETBALL.
I don't want to sing. I'm just a normal boy.
I just want to play basketball with my friends and get my head in the game. I can't sing!
I'm just Troy.
Get it together, Gibriella. We don't have time for extracurriculars, we have to get into college!
I'm not like other girls, I just want to stay at home and read books.
バカみたい 子供なのね
So foolish. You are a child.
夢を追って傷ついて
Chased dreams and got hurt.
嘘が下手なくせに 笑えない顔見せた
Even though you're bad at lies, you showed a humorless smile.
I love youも ろくに言わない
You can't even say "I love you" properly.
口下手で ほんまに不器用
Clumsy and really awkward with words.
なのはなのにどうして サヨナラは言えたの
Even so, why could you say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
This is no good, no good, no good at all.
あんたが好きで 好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much.
どれだけ 強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the drink,
歪まない思い出が バカみたい
The memories won't blur; what a fool.
馬鹿みたい 本当馬鹿ね
So foolish. Truly stupid.
あんた信じるばかりで
All I did was believe in you.
切なさの夜風浴びる
Bathing in the sorrowful night wind.
一人になって 3年が過ぎ
It's been 3 years since I became alone,
街並みさえも 変わりました
even the cityscape has changed.
なのに なのに どうして
Even so, even so, why?
未練だけ 置きざり
Only regrets are left behind.
ほんまに ロクな おとこやない
You truly are not a good man.
そろいの 指環 はずします
I take off our matching rings.
ざまみろ せいせいするわ
"This is what you deserve!" I feel relieved.
いい加減 まっても 馬鹿みたい
Even if I wait forever... What a fool.
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
This is no good, no good, no good at all.
あなたが 好きで 好きすぎて
I love you, I love you too much.
どれだけ 強い お酒でも
No matter how strong the drink,
歪まない 思い出が 馬鹿みたい
the memories are never muddied; what a fool.
ほんまに ロクな おとこやない
You truly are not a good man.
そろいの 指環 はずします
I take off our matching rings.
ざまみろ せいせいするわ
"This is what you deserve!" I feel relieved.
なんないのよ この涙
What are these tears?
馬鹿みたい
What a fool.
Woah, yeah, yeah.
Musicals is where it's at.
I think... I think this could really be
This is gonna get us the big dollars.
Yeah, hopefully the big mouse is not gonna shoot us in the head.
Ten billion dollars!
What big mouse?
Ten... don't worry about it. Ten
billion dollars! Yeah, it's really good.
We might need like a different type of show too, you know? Just for variety so...
They can't shoot us. Shoot us a variety show?
Yeah! Like a variety game show?
Yeah, The Autofister Games. The Autofister...
Physical Games! Physicals!
105!
Woah!
Slow down there, partner!
Hold your horses! Don't you think you're scrolling a little too fast?
Yeah, put down the phone and full-screen our video instead, because we are about to show you the new hot items in town!
Introducing the... Autofister Network!
Get it? 'Cause it's Autofister Network, but this is our merch.
We wanted to take this opportunity to show you all of our cool fun merch before it goes live!
We've got Cemimis, Gimimis, Grems, Otomos,
and this neat acrylic stand of the both of us! Yay!
And if you hurry up, you'll even be able to get the limited set with a postcard signed by both of us!
Woohoo! It will be live at this exact time, so make sure to check it out then!
Coming soon to a stream near you!
And we're back from our commercial break! Quick, who opened for waiting?
Welcome back to the official... Autofister...
Physical Autofister!
100!
And with us, we have our lovely contestants!
Bae! I'm Bae, I'm gonna win!
Su! Su-chan!
Fubuki! Scaramouche!
Towa! Towa-sama!
And as said before, we're here to find out
who's the ultimate winner of Physical Autofister!
100! Okay!
And played before our commercial break, each contestant will have to compete in our physical obstacle course of fun!
If you're just now tuning in, here's a quick recap.
Everyone starts in a line. You have to run to the other side while avoiding obstacles,
and do a quick little physical activity, grab a question from a dragon who telepathically gives it to your brain,
run back and answer a question.
We'll do four rounds, and the person with the most points at the end of four rounds is the winner!
Yay! Woohoo! Okay!
Well, everyone get into position.
Yeah!
Let's go! Let's go!
Okay, okay, okay, I think something's very big in there.
What is this?
It's so- so- as said before, of course, since a lot of these questions will be in English,
they have a handicap. To the handicap.
Very, very simple question.
What is this? Nice!
Yes, yes. The first run. The first round is you run over there,
and do five jumping jacks.
Five jumping jacks!
Five jumping jacks! Five jumping jacks!
Okay, are you ready? Three, two, one, go!
I was constrained! Please read the question out loud!
Okay, eto, the I like... Strawberry!
Question: Name a fruit! Strawberry!
Name a fruit! Strawberry! One point!
You can give your questions over here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Well, next round, next round. Is everyone ready?
No, no, no, we have to explain. Yeah, but is everyone ready for the next round?
Step hountarou. We're not the crab walk like this?
Crab walk like this! Crab walk!
Hey, come on!
Crab walk and five squats!
Crab walk under five squats!
Wait, do they have to jump?
No, they can- walk- wait, jump!
Jump! They have to jump!
Okay, everyone ready? Three, two, one, go!
13 x 6 = ?
78!
Yay! She's kind of really good at math.
She's good at math! Wow!
What color is a banana? When's the last time you ate a banana?
Why is it written in Japanese?!
I was given a handicap because the questions are in English, different in Japanese.
Do I still have to go around and around? Yes!
On my telepathy paper, the next one is sexy walk.
Sexy walk! Sexy walk!
Do we get disqualified? Do we have to start again if it's not sexy enough?
No!
Yes! Ha, please make up your mind.
We'll see. And three push-ups!
Three!
Okay. And sexy walk!
Sexy walk! Sexy walk! Sexy walk!
If the sexies are not enough, maybe youchi- you'll redo it.
Sexy is not enough! Sexy, sexy!
Make sure- make sure. Sexy jump!
Okay, we'll see.
Everyone ready?
Okay.
3, 2, 1,
Go!
Sexy, your babe! I'm...
You try, what is sexy?
1, 2, 3, 4!
Sukuwatto!
Squats!
Sukuwatto wa!
Sexy! Oh, sexy, sexy!
It's more sexy, you know! Sexy step has to take!
Sexy new turn!
Where is sexy visitor?
Sexy! Sexy! Sexy!
What again?
What? What?
Wait, sexy janai! Sexy janai!
Wait, not sexy! Not sexy!
You try run step, step, sexy!
It's like you only have to do it on the way... on the way back you can go straight.
Nah, nah. Hey, hey, it's not helpful to contest it.
Wait.
Eh?
Name a flower!
Eh... Pansy!
Oh, yeah!
Pansy!
Eh? Is it true? Oh, yeah! Pansy!
Wow! Okay, you got the crown! Okay!
1, 1, 1!
Wait, did you? Did you?
Have you been counting the points?
Yeah, 1, 1, 1!
Oh, really? 1, 1, 1?
1, 1, 1!
Oh! High breaker!
High breaker!
Okay, okay, last round!
Okay, okay. Saigo no point wa?
Okay, okay. What's the final point?
Are you ready?
100 points? 100 points?
100 points?
Last round!
Can I get rid of this?
No! Last round!
Do this. You have to do this well.
Okay. Lunge walk!
Eh?! Kitsu!
Eh?! Tough!
Yaba!
And then... Kita, kita, kita! Sankai!
And then... It's here, here, here! Three times!
Okay, okay.
How many times? Sankai! Sankai, sankai, sankai!
How many times? Three times! Three times, three times!
Sankai! Sankai!
Three times! Three times!
Sankai!
Three times!
Eh? Wow, you're so good!
Wow! You're so good!
Wow!
Okay, okay. Ganbaro!
Okay, okay. Let's do our best!
Ganbaro! Wakarimashita?
Let's do our best! Understood?
Okay! Okay desu! Wakarimashita.
Okay! Understood.
Shisu sou na kao.
You look like you're about to die.
Me too, me too!
Can I sue this?
No! No, no, no! All buttons will get cut soon!
Come on, come on! They're fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Everyone, ganbaro!
Everyone, do your best!
Last, last! Depi, one, two!
1, go!
Hey! Get to the ground, babe!
Kokonda suteru no?
Are you throwing it away here?
Foisah!
Heave-ho!
Foisah! Hai, yoni-san touching the...
Heave-ho! Hey, Yoni-san touching the...
Well, she's almost fine. She's doing her best!
It's knee!
Knee!
Furi! Furi! Wow! Disqualified!
Shake! Shake! Wow! Disqualified!
Okay! Foisah! Foisah! Foisah! Foisah! Foisah!
Okay! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Wait, let's wait for Bae to come back.
Oh, Bae, come on! Come on, Bae!
We can answer, Bae! Come on!
Come on, Bae! We can't... we can't decide the winner until you get over here!
Come on, Bae! We can't decide the winner until you get over here!
Hai! Hai! Hai, hai, hai, hai, hai, hai, hai, hai!
Hey! Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, you need to high five!
Hey, squat over here!
Hey, hey! Come on, come on, come on! Wow!
All right, here's your question.
Say a French word!
Oh!
Et souda?
Et soudain?
French?
French? French?
Itte masu ka ne?
Are you saying it?
Bonjour!
Oh!
Okay!
The winner! The winner!
The winner! The winner of today!
Katouki ne! Ni-san ni kayo!
Katouki! Go two steps back!
Haah!
Well, if the contestants have something to complain about, no matter what we do...
Yeah, we did our best! Yeah!
But they should try to... the last reload was like insane!
Yatteminai yo! Yatte isshuni... isshu mawatte...
You haven't done it! Do it together... spin around...
Kekkou hiroi yo!
It's quite wide!
No, no, no, no, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop! Bae, Bae only!
Eh? Bae only?
Bae only!
Bae only ka!
It's Bae only!
Security! Security!
Yeah, security!
Security! Security! Don't worry, I got her! Security!
Can you give her a crown?
Your crown!
Yay! (Hey, hey, hey...)
This is unfair! Please leave! Quick, quick! Cut break, cut break!
This is Bae! This is Su! This is Da-sama!
And you're watching the Autofister Network!
The rats sucked.
Yeah. Should go back to... should go back to the gym or something.
She should go back to school and retake PE.
Yeah, but Towa-sama was really strong! Wow, she even got the cool crown, amazing!
And Sue is so cute!
So cute!
Yo! Yo!
Also the hosts were amazing.
The hosts were so beautiful!
Every time they're on the screen, I was electrified.
I think this is what's going to get us the funding.
Yeah, I think we're going to get $10 million for this one.
And the more budget they have, the more difficult the challenges can get.
And then the death, you know, the penalty can be even greater.
Anyways, what if anime...
...but live action?
I don't feel so good.
Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah... Ah...
I'm so tired, Gigi.
Me too. I'm so tired 'cause we worked so hard.
We've been working so hard with making so many shows
and so sleepy as I would record in the studio every single day!
They've always over-invited me to their tea parties!
I've always over-invited them to their tea parties!
You know what? Actually, I have been preparing something.
Is it this background?
Yes, yes. It's a really realistic background
that you probably stole from the internet.
Yeah, I stole it. I stole it.
Stole it from the internet.
Yeah, and this is my tea party. So welcome in!
It's um, but yeah, I have one more surprise, Gigi.
A surprise for a tea party?
Yeah, where are models?
Where's me? Where's me?
You know what? We got some graphics update.
A graphic update?
You want to see?
I want to see me! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. It's me!
Cecilia Immergreen from Hololive EN!
Just this spin, twin, you look great!
Yo, thanks! You look freakishly amazing!
I guess I'll go sit down real quick.
Oh, my god, I look so good.
Look at my shoes look so good. Wow!
Hey Gigi, come on, come on in. It's okay. Oh, I get one too? Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Gigi Murin everyone! It's Gigi Murin from Hololive English Justice!
I'm so happy to be here.
Wow, you look great too! I guess it's time for me to sit down also.
Look at my shoes too.
Wow. Wow. Wow. Those look good. Those look kind of hard to walk in actually. That's crazy.
No, I have a natural... Let me sit down, sit down, sit down already.
And together, we are...
Autofist! Autofist! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Finally, we get some time to relax.
Wow, you look really good.
Addate, you look really good. Oh, are we hugging again?
Oh, I just can't... I just really like hugging you. I can't help it. I keep hugging you.
I really like hugging, I guess.
Oh, my hood came off. That's fine.
I'm so excited! So excited!
I'm really happy to be here.
Oh, are you hungry?
I'm really hungry. Will you feed me?
Okay, I'll feed you. I'll feed you. Say ah.
Ah. Ah.
Oh, accidentally. Oh, I'm really hungry too.
Oh, my god, I'm... I'm...
Oh, you're getting this all over me. It even really messed...
Oh, why are you getting on your face too? Eww. The texture is really... Let me feed you again.
Do you mind if I got my spit on it? You don't mind, do you?
Wait, wait. Let me wipe that up. You... you... you got something on the side of your mouth.
Let me just... Let me just get that for you.
Are you so... Let me get it off of you too.
Oh, you have something on your mouth.
Oh, okay, okay, that's enough. That's enough.
Thirsty?
Um, I'm thirsty. I'm really thirsty.
Okay, I'll pour you some tea.
Look, look, look, look.
I'm really... I'm really excited.
Here's your tea.
It's really hot.
Oh, be careful. Be careful.
Oh, my god. It's really... Oh, my god. It's really hot.
Oh, it's really on my nose. Oh, god. Oh, it's...
Oh, no, you spilled it. Oh, my god. Ah, it's hot.
Oh, no, you spilled it! Oh, my god, it's hot!
Oh, my god, it burns. Ah, tsuey! Ah, tsuey! Oh, my god.
Oh, it burns! Ow! Ow! Oh, my god!
I am... Oh, no.
I feel like I got a third-degree burn just now.
Why did you do that to you? You picked me. Ah, ow. Let me cool your... Let me wipe it off of you.
Hey, sorry, I didn't mean to do that. I just got really overzealous.
Mm, but it's really good now, it's cool down.
You like it? What type of tea is it?
Oh, it's like a nice little floral note on it.
Here, try some. Try from my finger. Try from my finger.
How's the taste? Yummy!
That's really...
Okay, okay, that's... that's enough.
I finished my cup. It was really... it was really delicious.
You know, if Liz was here, she would tell us that after having a really good meal,
we should work out.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so let's get up.
Let's go. Stand over there in this corner.
Yeah, let's stand by the horse.
That horse is really amazing.
So much noise.
Sorry, my...
My shoes are just really big and clunky.
You know what? I think it'd be really cool if we were to do 50 push-ups right now.
I...
I want to do...
You know what? I want to do 50 push-ups too.
Me?
I really want to...
No, no, no, no, no.
I really want to do 50 push... Okay, okay, wait. I changed my mind.
Well, she...
I want, I want, um, 50 lunges.
50 lunges?
Oh, oh, oh, your knee hurts?
Ow.
Ah, I think, yeah, I got into an accident about 200 years ago.
Did you get a hit by a car?
I got hit by a car 200 years ago.
Oh, okay.
I guess that's just how it is.
You know what? Chigi Morin.
Don't touch me.
Stop touching me.
What?
Oh, my god. You're always whiny.
You're always whiny with me.
Your knees, oh, you are fighting...
No, I hate you.
I hate you.
I hate you so much.
I hate your hair.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I got... Sorry, I was getting mean.
I was acting out.
Will you forgive me?
I guess so.
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
And didn't mean to. Can you kiss my knee, please?
I guess, oh, I feel really good now.
Do you feel better?
I feel better.
And I feel really sleepy all of a sudden.
Me too, actually.
I'm so sleepy.
I'm so sleepy too.
Ah, but there's only one bed.
What should we do? Should we get in together?
I get... Get? So...
I guess well get into...
Let me just take off my shoes first.
Oh, yeah.
I think it would be really, really weird to get into bed with shoes on.
Yeah, that would be strange.
Well, let me help you.
Let me fluff this pillow for you. Oh, you look so... Here you go, princess.
Okay, let me... Let me just lay down.
Oh, let me get into bed.
I'll take my shoes off, too.
I'm already getting so comfortable.
Please, please, don't go to bed without me.
I'm so tired. If someone doesn't get into bed quick, I'm just going to fall asleep without you.
Oh, no, don't, don't.
It's just my... My achy, achy bones.
I'm trying to get to bed, please.
I guess your knee really hurts still.
It does.
Oh, I feel so comfortable.
Thanks for coming to my tea party, Chigi Morin.
Thanks for inviting me, CC.
Good night.
Oh, we're holding our hands.
That's because I get scared in the dark.
Oh, of course. Yeah.
Yeah, so I'm glad that we have each other.
Good night, CC.
Good night, Chigi.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good night.
みんないが大好きっ!!
I'm CC,
延々続行 ルーララ Miracle Sing Time
and I'm Chigi.
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
And you're watching...
つたない曲でも 妙な歌詞でも
The Autofist Network!
Umm...
I don't know, that's going to make us any money.
Well, onto the next idea.
みんなが大好きっ!!
I love everyone!
延々続行 ルーララ Miracle Sing Time
It goes on forever, Lu la la Miracle Sing Time.
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I sing and sing to convey my love the best I can.
つたない曲でも 妙な歌詞でも
Even if the song sucks, even if the lyrics are questionable,
届けたい 一番のsoulを
I want to deliver my soul with all my heart.
どうしよう オートマチックに決められてる
What should I do? Things are being decided for me automatically.
時間割りじゃ追いつかないの
I can't keep up with the schedule.
夢無限 したいこと怒涛
Wanting to dream infinitely is an angry wave,
廊下もダッシュで集まるの
we'll get together with a dash down the hallway.
テンション上昇 ルーララ Powerful Gig Time
The tension keeps rising, Lu la la Powerful Gig Time.
ハートって ハートって ワクワク探す天才
The heart, the heart is a genius at searching for excitement.
アレっ!?って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if they go "Huh!?", even if I keep messing up,
放ちたい 湧いてくるbraveを
I want to release my overflowing bravery.
しかけるトレモロ 応えるフラム
I'll start a tremolo, a flam will respond.
いいじゃん いいじゃん ノリノリでんじゃない?
It's great, it's great. Isn't it great to be high-spirited?!
ハッピーはいつだってね “今”感じるもの
Happiness is something we always feel in the present.
生きろ少女 本能で、裸の
Girls, live strong with your bare instincts.
大好きっ!!
I really love it!!
テンション最高 ルーララ Wonderful Show Time
The tension is at its best, Lu la la Wonderful Show Time.
鳴らして 鳴らして 私達のMusic
We'll play and play our music as we like.
拍手も 賞賛も 観客もゼロでも
Even if there's no standing ovation, a prize, or an audience,
奏でたい 今 この一瞬を
I want to play in this real instance.
“昨日の後悔”も“明日の憂鬱”も
"Yesterday's regrets" and "tomorrow's worries",
ぶっつけちちゃって ぶっつけちちゃって 誰? 何?
I'll be blunt about it - who's it? What's it?
ラッキーはいつだってね “今”掴むもの
Luck is something we always catch in the present.
輝け少女 望むなら、自分を
Be eager, girls - if you're not given it, then bid farewell.
教科書にはないし クラスじゃ教えない
It's not written in any book and I don't get taught any bit of it in class,
だけど忘れない
But I won't ever forget...
みんなが大好きっ!!
Everyone's favorite!!
延々続行 ルーララ Miracle Sing Time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la miracle sing time!
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, the ultimate way to express my love!
つたない曲でも 妙な歌詞でも
Even if the tune is clumsy or the lyrics are odd,
届けたい 一杯のsoulを
I want to deliver my soul with all I have!
どうしよう オートマティックに 決められてる 時間割りじゃ追いつかないの
What can we do? We can't keep up with the schedule set automatically.
夢無限 したいこと怒涛 廊下もダッシュで集まるよ
Infinite dreams, a flood of things to do, rushing down the hall to gather!
お行儀悪かったらsorry! でもなりふりも構わずに
Sorry if my manners are bad! But without caring how I look,
どっぷりハマっちゃうplay キラリっって もしかこれが青春
Totally addicted to play, sparkling—maybe this is youth!
ever ever...Forever Shine
Ever ever... Forever Shine
本当に大好きっ!!
I really love you!!
テンション上昇 ルーララ Powerful Gig Time
Tension rising, lu-la-la powerful gig time!
ハートって ハートって ワクワク探す天才
Heart after heart, a genius searching for excitement!
アレッ!?って言われても ミス連発でも
Even if people say "Huh!?" or I keep making mistakes,
放ちたい 湧いてくるbraveを
I want to release the surging bravery!
かけるトレモロ 応えるフラム
Tremolo ringing out, followed by a flam.
ハッピーはいつだってね “今”感じるもの
Happiness is always what you feel right "now."
生きろ乙女 本能で、裸の
Live on, maidens, with your bare instincts!
どうしても ホームワークよりも重要課題
No matter what, it's more important than homework:
放課後のお茶おしゃべり 練習
After-school tea, chatting, and practice.
ユーモア ナチュラル めくるめく笑い
Humor, natural, spinning around with laughter,
ウケ過ぎでお腹痛い 呼吸ぴっしちexcellent!
stomach hurting from laughing too hard, breathing perfectly—excellent!
でも苦手なリフまもあったの 特訓付きあってくれる
But there were riffs I wasn't good at—will you help me practice?
never never...can't say good-bye
Never never... can't say good-bye.
本当に大好きっ!!
I really love you!!
テンション上昇 ルーララ Wonderful Show Time
Tension rising, lu-la-la wonderful show time!
音楽って 音楽って すでに私たち!
Music is, music is already us!
スタンディングオベーションも賞も観客なくても
Even without standing ovations, awards, or an audience,
演じたい この瞬間をリアルに
We want to live this moment for real.
昨日の後悔 明日の心配
Yesterday's regrets, tomorrow's worries—
ぶっちぎれ ぶっちぎれ なんだっけ?誰得?
blow right past them! What was it again? Who benefits?
ハッピーはいつだってね “今”つかむもの
Happiness is always what you grasp "now."
欲張り乙女 あげないならさようなら
Greedy maidens, if you won't give it, say goodbye!
どの教科書にも載ってない 教室じゃちょっと教えてくれない
Not in any textbook, not taught in a classroom,
だけど一生忘れない
but I'll never forget it as long as I live.
ありえない奇跡 歌うよ!!Miracle
An impossible miracle—let's sing!! Miracle!
信じられる 強くなれる!
I can believe, I can grow strong!
みんなが大好きっ!!
Everyone's favorite!!
延々続行 ルーララ Miracle Sing Time
It's our never-ending lu-la-la miracle sing time!
歌って 歌って 愛伝える最強手段
I'll sing, I'll sing, the ultimate way to express my love!
つたない曲でも 妙な歌詞でも
Even if the tune is clumsy or the lyrics are odd,
届けたい 精一杯のsoulとlarger-than-life life
I want to deliver my soul and a larger-than-life life with all I have!
昨日と同じ 今日と同じ明日?
Is tomorrow just like today, just like yesterday?
いーじうん いーじうん 楽しんだもの勝ち!
It's fine, it's fine, whoever has the most fun wins!
私はロッカー “今”反抗期
I'm a rocker, "now" is my rebellious phase.
スメ乙女 希望抱いて!
Push forward, maidens, embrace your hopes!
大好き 大好き 愛してくれてありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for loving me!
歌うよ 歌うよ 今日も精一杯
I'll sing, I'll sing, with all my heart again today!
大好き 大好き 愛してくれてありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for loving me!
歌うよ 歌うよ ずっと愛を歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, I'll sing of love forever!
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for the love!
歌うよ 歌うよ 心込めて今日も歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, putting my heart into it again today!
大好き 大好き 大好きをありがとう
I love you, I love you, thank you for the love!
歌うよ 歌うよ 愛を込めてずっと歌うよ
I'll sing, I'll sing, singing of love forever!
ずっと愛を歌うよ
I'll sing of love forever!
Please hold.
We will soon be changing the channel.
We are about to switch the channel.
Please wait.
The channels will be changed soon.
Please stay seated as the channels are about to switch.
Don't change the channel, because we'll do it for you.
Do not touch the remote, because we will be doing it.